<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bicep on The blog of Kewalaka</title><link>https://blog.kewalaka.nz/tags/bicep/</link><description>Recent content in bicep on The blog of Kewalaka</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 07:32:14 +1300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.kewalaka.nz/tags/bicep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Azure Verified Modules</title><link>https://blog.kewalaka.nz/p/2023/09/azure-verified-modules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 07:32:14 +1300</pubDate><guid>https://blog.kewalaka.nz/p/2023/09/azure-verified-modules/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.kewalaka.nz/p/2023/09/azure-verified-modules/avm.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Azure Verified Modules" />&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://aka.ms/AVM" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Azure Verified Modules&lt;/a> is an initiative in development from Microsoft that seeks to unify many previous attempts to standardarise Infrastructure as Code modules on the Azure platform. The initiative aims to establish strategy, governance, and create a brand that becomes the go to place for resources &amp;amp; patterns, currently targeting Bicep and Terraform.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s aim is to &amp;ldquo;consolidate and set the standards for what a good Infrastructure-as-Code module looks like&amp;rdquo;, following the principles of the &lt;a class="link" href="http://aka.ms/WAF" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Well Architected Framework&lt;/a>, evolving existing efforts such as the &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/Azure/ResourceModules" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>CARML library for Bicep resources&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m particularly excited to see the direction for the Terraform modules, this would benefit from such a focal point, and I hope it will unify what I believe has been a fragmented ecosystem on the Azure platform.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The initiative is at an early stage, and not yet open to contributions outside of Microsoft, but if you&amp;rsquo;re interested or working in the DevOps space on the Azure platform, I believe this is one to watch!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>